Guide to the Kathy Acker Papers, 1972-1997 and undated RL.00011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kathy Acker papers
1972-1997 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997
RL.00011
21.0 Linear Feet
0.03 Gigabytes
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Also, some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Furthermore, all or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Kathy Acker Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 1999-2002, 2012, 2014.
Biographical Note
1948 Born.
1963-65 Studied Classics at Brandeis University.
1967 Received BA from University of California at San Diego (UCSD).
1968-1970 Studied at UCSD Department of Literature.
1971 Studied at New York University Classics Department.
1975 Published The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula.
1975-1976 Creative Artists' Public Services Program New York State Grant For Fiction.
1978 Published Kathy Goes to Haiti.
1980 Published I Dreamt I Became A Nymphomaniac: Imagining.
1980 Published The Adult Life of Toulouse-Lautrec.
1980-1981 Instructor, The San Francisco Art Institute, Video and Performance Department.
1981 Pushcart Prize.
1982 Published Hello, I'm Erica Jong.
1983 Published Great Expectations.
1984 Published Algeria: A Series of Invocations Because Nothing Else Works.
1984 Published Blood and Guts in High School.
1986 Published Don Quixote.
1988 Published Empire of the Senseless.
1988 My Death, My Life, By Pier Paolo Pasolini published in Literal Madness.
1989 Published Young Lust; Kathy Goes to Haiti; The Adult Life of Toulouse Lautrec; Florida.
1990 Published The Seven Cardinal Virtues.
1990 Published In Memoriam to Identity.
1991 Published Hannibal Lecteur, My Father.
1991-1995 Adjunct Professor, San Francisco Art Institute.
1992 Published Portrait of an Eye: Three Novels.
1993 Published My Mother Demonology.
1994 Visiting Professor, UCSD.
1994 Visiting Professor, University of California at Santa Barbara.
1994 Visiting Professor, University of Idaho.
1996 Published Pussy, King of the Pirates.
1997 Died.
Collection Overview
The papers of Kathy Acker, 1975-1996 and undated, are comprised, for the most part, of manuscript drafts of her novels, short stories, and other miscellaneous writings ranging from early works such as The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula (1975) to her last novel Pussy, King of the Pirates (1996). Described as a cyberpunk author and performance artist, Acker's novels question the strictures of female sexuality and the power of language.
CD-ROMs; Color slides; Color photographs; Machine-readable records; Black-and-white negatives; Audiocassettes; American fiction -- 20th century; American fiction -- Women authors; Color negatives; Phonograph records; Experimental fiction -- Women authors; Punk culture -- United States -- Fiction; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Correspondence; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997
- Writings
  - Fiction, 1973-1996 and undated; 17 boxes
    - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula, 3 folders
      Scope and Contents
      The volumes of The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula were self-published and distributed by Kathy Acker. The novel was presented in six serialized parts, usually mailed to subscribers, friends, and potentially interested parties. Volumbes 1 and 3 are text sheets cut to size and mounted. Volumes 1-5 bear Ron Silliman's small ownership stamp.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula by the The Black Tarantula (published copy), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #1, June 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Part one of six parts titled "Intention: I become a murderess by repeating in words the lives of other murderesses." 37 pages.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #2, June 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Part two of six parts entitled: "A point-to-point comparison between my life and the life of Moll Catpurse, the Queen-Regent of Misrule, the Roaring Girl, the benevolent tyrant of city thieves and city murderers, the Bear Lady." 11 pages.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #3, July; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Part three of six parts entitled: "A secret document: I move to San Francisco, I begin to copy my favorite pornography books and become the main person in each of them." 21 pages.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #4, July 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Part four of six parts entitled: "I become Helen Seferis, and then, Alexander Trocchi." 46 pages.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #5, September 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Part five of six parts entitled: "I explore my miserable childhood: I become William Butler Yeats." 29 pages.
      - The Childlike Life of the Black Tarantula #6, September; 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Part six of six parts, entitled: "The story of my life." 28 pages.
    - Ripoff Red: Girl Detective, 1 folders
      - Ripoff Red: Girl Detective, (typescript), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - I Dreamt I Became/Was a Nymphomaniac, 2 folders
      - I Dreamt I Became/Was a Nymphomaniac (5 staple-bound, clean copies), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - I Dreamt I Became/Was a Nymphomaniac (staple-bound copies, annotated set), 1-6 and unnumbered, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The Adult Life of Tolouse Lautrec, 1 folders
      - The Adult Life of Toulouse Lautrec (published copy), 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Bum, 1 folders
      - The Bum (typescript plus one holograph page), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Florida, 1 folders
      - Florida (annotated typescript), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Kathy Goes to Haiti, 2 folders
      - Kathy Goes to Haiti (bound typescript), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Kathy Goes to Haiti (proofs), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Girl Gangs Take Over the World, 1 folders
      - Girl Gangs Take Over the World (annotated typescript), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Algeria, 1 folders
      - Algeria: A Series of Invocations Because Nothing Else Works (typescript), undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Great Expectations, 3 folders
      - Great Expectations (annotated typescripts), undated; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
      - Great Expectations (annotated proofs), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - New York City in 1979, 1 folders
      - New York City in 1979 (annotated typescripts) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Time, 1 folders
      - Time (annotated typescripts), 1981 and undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Blood and Guts in High School, 6 folders
      - Blood and Guts in High School (annotated typescript), undated; 2 folders (Box 3-4, Folder 6, 1)
      - Blood and Guts in High School (annotated proofs), undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Blood and Guts in High School plus two (copies 1-2) (proofs), 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
      - Blood and Guts: Farsi text originals (holograph), undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - My Death, My Life, 2 folders
      - My Death, My Life by Pier Paolo Pasolini (annotated typescript), 1982; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - Don Quixote, 3 folders
      - Rejects from Don Quixote (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Don Quixote Vol. 1, 3 (annotated typescript), 1984-1985 and undated (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - Arthur Rambaud Was Homosexual, 1 folders
      - Arthur Rimbaud was Homosexual (annotated typescript), undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Empire of the Senseless, 1 folders
      - Empire of the Senseless, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lust/A Sailor's Slight Identity, 1 folders
      - Lust/A Sailor's Slight Identity (annotated typescript with holographic notes), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dead Doll Humility, 1 folders
      - Dead Doll Humility (annotated typescript), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - In Memoriam to Identity, 4 folders
      - In Memoriam to Identity (annotated typescript), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
      - In Memoriam to Identity (1) (annotated typescript), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - In Memoriam to Identity (2) (annotated typescript), undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - J., 1 folders
      - J. (annotated typescript), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - My Mother: Demonology, 13 film feet
      - My Mother: Demonology (annotated typescript), 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
      - My Mother: Demonology (1) (annotated typescript), 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - My Mother: Demonology (2) (annotated typescript), 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - My Mother: Demonology (proofs), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapters 1 and 2: My Mother (2 notebooks), undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 3: Clit City (5 notebooks), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 4: Obsession (3 notebooks), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 5 and miscellaneous (5 notebooks), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 6: Redoing Childhood (3 notebooks), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 6: Redoing Childhood (annotated typescript), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - My Mother: Demonology, Chapter 7: The Dead Man (4 notebooks), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pussy, King of the Pirates, 6 boxes
      - Dream of a Passage Out of Childhood (annotated typescript), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Story of O in which Everyone's an Animal (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - O and Ange Beginning (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Second Chapter-Beginning of O and Ange (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - O and Ange Tell Each Other their Dreams about Men (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - The World Without Men/Thru the Cunts of Our Mothers (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Escape (1 notebook) (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - The Loneliness of the Weasel Cat (1 notebook), undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - The Point of Everything (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - III. First Draft, First Part (2 notebooks), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Before I Left with the Pirates (1 notebook and 1 annotated booklet), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - In the Days of the Pirates (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Virgin Gold Returns (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - The Creation of the Wor(l)d According to Dog (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Second Part-Final Draft- p. 1 Becoming a Rat (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Journey to the Pirates (1 notebook), undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - In the Deep of America (1 notebook), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Ariadne (1 notebook) (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Part II: Entering the World (1 notebook), undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - 2nd Part: O After Pussycat (1 notebook), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - 2nd Draft: After Pussycat (1 notebook), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - O After Pussycat I/Sex (1 notebook) (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Dream Maps (2 notebooks and 5 hand-drawn maps), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - All is Sex (1 notebook) (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Pussy and the Pirates (1 notebook), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - The Dreams of Pirates (1 notebook), undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Ostracism (2 notebooks), undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Antigone (3 notebooks), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - The Book of Desire (1 notebook), undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Bast is Baba (1 notebook), undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - The Old World of China (1 notebook), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - China Revolution Whores (1 notebook), undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Looking for a Pussycat (annotated typescript), undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Days That Are to Come (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - The Vision Passes (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Pirate Island (annotated typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Ostracism's Story (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - In the Days of the Pirates (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates, pp. 1-185 (annotated typescript), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates, pp. 185A-328 (annotated typescript), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates (typescript in red binder), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates, pp 1-164 (typescript), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates, pp. 165-327 (typescript), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Pussy, King of the Pirates, Table of contents-pp. 89 (typescript), undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Antigone's Story (typescript), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Excerpts (holograph page and typescripts, some annotated), 1995 and undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Eurydice in the Underworld, 9 folders
      - Eurydice in the Underworld, Euridice Rises (1 notebook), undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Eurydice Seeing Visions (1 notebook), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Eurydice's Monologue (1 notebook), undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Eurydice Speaks (1 notebook), undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Orpheus in the Underworld (1 notebook and 8 pages of notes), undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Eurydice in the Underworld, excerpts (1 of 3) (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Eurydice in the Underworld, excerpts (2 of 3) (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Eurydice in the Underworld, excerpts (3 of 3) (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Eurydice in the Underworld, excerpts (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Breaking Through Memories Into Desire: I Become Jane Eyre Who Rebelled Against Everyone, 1973
      - First Part of "Breaking Through Memories Into Desire" typescript, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        Likely intended to be another serial publication, but never finished or distributed.
  - Poetry, 1972; 1 folders
    - Homage to Leroi Jones (typescript), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Drama, 1981-1996 and undated; 1 boxes
    - The Birth of the Poet (annotated typescript), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - The Birth of the Poet (typescript), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Birth of the Poet in So & So vol. 2 no. 1 (4 copies), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Requiem Drafts (2 Notebooks), undated (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
    - Requiem (annotated typescripts), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Music, 1996; 3 folders
    - Pussy, King of the Pirates CD by the Mekons with Kathy Acker (1 of 3) (annotated typescripts), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pussy, King of the Pirates CD by the Mekons with Kathy Acker (2 of 3) (annotated typescripts), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Pussy, King of the Pirates CD by the Mekons with Kathy Acker (3 of 3), 1996; 2 disks (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Essays, 1979-1997; 3 boxes
    Conditions Governing Access
    Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
    - Notes on Writing from the Life of Baudelaire (typescript and publication copy), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - New York City 1983 (annotated typescript) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Blue Valentine (typescript), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - A Few Notes on Two of my Books (typescript), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - William Burroughs' Realism (typescript), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - New York City 25/12/89-31/12/89 at the Edge of the New (2 annotated typescripts), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - The Language of Sex The Sex of Language (3 typescripts), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - The End of Poetry (1 notebook) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - In the Underworld (2 typescripts), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - From Counter-Culture to Culture, But Here's no Culture/Fuck Ecology and the Death of Communism/The Meaning of the 80s (2 typescripts), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bodybuilding (1 typescript), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Red Wings (1 typescript), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Language of the Body (2 notebooks, 1 typescript, 1 publication copy), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Reading the Lack of the Body: The Writing of the Marquis de Sade (1 typescript), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - After the End of the Art World (notes, typescript), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Moving Into Wonder, Intro to Time Capsule (annotated typescript, typescript), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Seeing Gender (notebook, notes, annotated typescript, typescript), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Running through the World: On the Art of Kiki Smith (notes, annotated typescripts, 3.5 inch floppy), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Mirror: Two Works of Art (2 typescripts, annotated typescript), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Samuel Delaney: Orpheus (typescript, annotated typescript), 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Delaney Edit electronic file, 1995; MS Word document extracted from 3.5" floppy disk; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL00011-SET-0002, Disk RL00011-FL3-0003)
    - Strange Gaze interview with Anton Corbijn (interview transcript, annotated typescript), 1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Separated Materials
      Original audiocassette of interview removed to Box 33.
    - A Girl is Reading William Burroughs (typescript), 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - The Gift of Disease (2 notebooks, loose notes, annotated typescript, typescripts), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Spiced with Girl Power Interview Drafts (photo with Acker, annotated typescripts), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Spiced with Girl Power Interview Transcript, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Spiced with Girl Power Spiral Notebook, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Spiced with Girl Power publicity, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Includes promotional audiovisual materials, including one mixtape produced by Town House Studios in London, and three promotional compact discs.
    - Spiced with Girl Power Mel B. Natal Chart by Kathy Acker, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Spice Girls interview transcript electronic files, 1997; Three MS Word documents extracted from a 3.5" floppy disk; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL00011-SET-0002, Disk RL00011-FL3-0002)
  - Video, 1983; 1 folders
    - Variety (annotated typescript), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Interviews, 1988; 1 folders
    - Interview: Kathy Acker in Red Bass (periodical), 1988 (Box 1988, Folder 5)
  - Film Reviews, 1989-1991; 2 folders
    - The War at Home: Bonfire of the Vanities by Brian de Palma (typescript), 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Review of Scandal for Weiner (typescript), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Book Reviews, 1985-1989; 1 folders
    - Book Reviews (typescripts of 16 different reviews), 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1989-1990; 1 folders
    - Letters to the Editor (3 typescripts of 1 letter; 1 typescript), 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, 1994-1995 and undated; 3 folders
    - Address to the Author's Guild (annotated typescripts, typescript, conference information), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Opening Speech for the Lahti Writers Reunion on the Question: Does Literature Come from Good or from Evil? (annotated typescript), undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Speech for the Artist in Society Conference (notes, research materials, annotated typescript, typescript), 1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Other Writings by Acker, 1972-1994; 2 boxes
    - About Robert Mapplethorpe (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - An Actual Institution of Art (annotated typescript), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Allen Ginsberg: A Personal Portrait (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Born for Trouble (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - The Boy I Want (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Bruce Willis and Me (annotated typescript), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - A Bunch of Propositions about the Hernandez Brothers (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Burroughs on Burroughs (typescripts), undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - By Cesar Vallejo (typescript), 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Christ Comes to New York City (typescripts), undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Collette (annotated typescript), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Comment on Pirates (notes), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Conversations (annotated typescript), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Current Reading (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Critical Languages (typescript), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Dear Santa (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - The Destruction of the US/The Burning Bombing of America (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Entrance into Dwelling in Paradise (typescript), 1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Eugenie De Franval (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Exercise #3: Writing Asystematically (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Fabre's Work or Opera (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Feminine Heroism (annotated typescript), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Fete (15 typescripts), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Freedom and Domination in the Theatre (annotated typescript), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Fucking Up Japanese (annotated typescript, typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - The Future (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Getting the Alphabet Right (annotated typescript, notes), undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - I'm Honored to Present the Award… (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - In 1894 General Jacob S. Coxey (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - An Informal Interview with Kathy Acker on the 23rd April, 1986 (typescript) (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - The Insoluble Problem of Violence (annotated typescript, typescript), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Interview of Juan Goytisolo (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Introduction: In Praise of Writing (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - I Return to B (Wuthering Heights) (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - I've Been Asked to Write Some Brief Words (typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Japan (annotated typescript), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Journal Black Cats Black Jewels (typescript), 1972 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Just Keep to Cold Facts (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Lady, Be Bad (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Looking for Madonna (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Loss/The Memory of Orpheus (annotated typescripts), undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Lullabye (typescript), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Memories of Electra (1 of 2) (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Memories of Electra (2 of 2) (annotated typescript), undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous writings electronic files, 1996; Text document files extracted from a ZIP disk; approximately 27 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL00011-SET-0002, Disk RL00011-ZIP-0001)
      Electronic files include writings by Acker.